Last Christmas, I gave you my heart
But the very next day
You gave it away
This year to save me from tears
I'll give it to someone special!
Last Christmas, I gave you my heart
But the very next day
You gave it away
This year to save me from tears
I'll give it to someone special!
Special!
Once bitten
And twice shy
I keep my distance
But you still catch my eye
Tell me baby
Do you recognize me?
Well it's been year
It doesn't surprise me
Happy Christmas!
I wrapped it up
And sent it
With a note saying
I LOVE YOU!!
I meant it!
Now I know
What! a fool
I've been
And if you kiss me now
I know you...
You'd fool me again
Last Christmas, I gave you my heart
But the very next day
You gave it away
Gave it away
This year to save me from tears
I'll give it to someone special!
Special!
Last Christmas, I gave you my heart
But the very next day
You gave it away
This year to save me from tears
I'll give it to someone special!
Special!
Oh!
Oh! baby
A crowded room
Friends with tired eyes
I am hiding from you
And your soul of ice
My God I thought you were
Someone to rely on
Me?  I guess I was a shoulder to cry on
A face-on lover
With a fire in her heart
A girl undercover but you
Tore me a part
Ooh-ooh
Now I found a real love you never
Fool me again.
Last Christmas, I gave you my heart
But the very next day
You gave it away
This year to save me from tears
I'll gave it to someone...
Special!
Last Christmas, I gave you my heart
But the very next day
You gave it away
This year to save me from tears
I'll gave it to someone...
Special!
A face-on lover
With a fire in her heart (I gave you my heart)
A girl undercover but you
Tore her apart
Maybe next year
I'll gave it to someone...
Special!